{
    "id": "bb60fbadf5d84c35830dd15e1da9d5a0",
    "title": "Make Negative Sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1bb62362be054437a96725090c715053",
            "title": "Negative Sentences Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... like to read science fiction.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do not",
                        "has not",
                        "not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Dogs .................................... chase cats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not",
                        "does not",
                        "do not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Dogs ................................ like to chase cats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not",
                        "do not",
                        "does not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Pete ....................................... not want to talk with Ann.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Alice ..................................... not work for an insurance company.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... not like this wine very much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................................... not enjoy playing with my kids.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sharon ...................................... not make models from clay.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ................................. practice the violin every morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does not",
                        "have not",
                        "do not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My brother ....................................... not earn two hundred dollars a week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team ................................. not play well yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................. not go to school by bus.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "has",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}